{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How many ______ the exam?",
      "options": [
        "a. students passed",
        "b. students did pass",
        "c. did pass",
        "d. did students pass"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "The longer you practice every day, _____.",
      "options": [
        "a. the best you will get",
        "b. better you'll get",
        "c. the better you'll get",
        "d. you'll get better"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "She is _____ woman.",
      "options": [
        "a. an American young intelligent",
        "b. a young intelligent American",
        "c.an intelligent young American",
        "d. an intelligent American young"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "I'm lucky to be surrounded by _____ fascinating people.",
      "options": ["a. such a", "b. so", "c. so much", "d. such"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "If they beat Manchester next weekend, they _____ ten successive games.",
      "options": [
        "a. are winning",
        "b. have won",
        "c. will have won",
        "d. will win"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "You can play outside when you ____ your lunch",
      "options": [
        "a. will have eaten",
        "b. have eaten",
        "c. are eating",
        "d. eat"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "_____ the answer if she hadn't helped you?",
      "options": [
        "a. Could you find",
        "b. Had you found",
        "c. Would you have found",
        "d. Would you find"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "I wish he _____ treating us like idiots. Who does he think he is?",
      "options": ["a. would stop", "b. stopped", "c. had stopped", "d. stops"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "I love cheese now, but I _____ like it as a child",
      "options": [
        "a. didn’t used to",
        "b. didn’t use to",
        "c. wasn’t used to",
        "d. usedn’t to"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "It _____ easy to win the tournament. All the teams were really good.",
      "options": [
        "a. mustn't have been",
        "b. shouldn't have been",
        "c. might not be",
        "d. can't have been"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "The attacker is thought _____ jumping from the second floor of the building.",
      "options": [
        "a. to escaped",
        "b. that he escaped",
        "c. to have escaped",
        "d. he has escaped"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "_____ said that is totally crazy.",
      "options": ["a. Whoever", "b. Whatever", "c. However", "d. Whenever"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "The new model comes in red or white but I don't like _____ of those colours.",
      "options": ["a. either", "b. neither", "c. none", "d. both"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "We _____ tomorrow morning. The train _____ at 7:45 a.m.",
      "options": [
        "a. will leave / leaves",
        "b. leave / is leaving",
        "c. are leaving / leaves",
        "d. leave / leaves"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ her since the day I met her.",
      "options": ["a. 've loved", "b. 'm loving", "c. love", "d. loving"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    }
  ]
}
